<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<BaseGameText>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>The Crownlands</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_ADJECTIVE">
			<Text>The Crownlands</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_THE_SILVER_PRINCE_NAME">
			<Text>The Silver Prince</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_THE_SILVER_PRINCE_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>+2 points of [ICON_GreatMusician] Great Musician from Capital City. +2 Slots of [ICON_GreatWork_Music] Great Works of Music to Palace. +1 Slot of [ICON_GreatWork_Music] Great Works of Music to each level of Government Plaza Building.[NEWLINE]Each [ICON_GreatWork_Music] Great Work of Music also yields +8 [ICON_Faith] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_QUOTE">
			<Text>He has a song. He is the prince that was promised, and his is the song of ice and fire. There must be one more. The dragon has three heads..</Text>
		</Row>

		<!--City Names-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CITY_1">
			<Text>King's Landing</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--CITIZEN NAMES-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_THE_CROWNLANDS_MALE_1">
			<Text>Marston Waters</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_THE_CROWNLANDS_MALE_2">
			<Text>Tyrion Tanner</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_THE_CROWNLANDS_MALE_3">
			<Text>Addam Velaryon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_THE_CROWNLANDS_MALE_4">
			<Text>Bartimos Celtigar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_THE_CROWNLANDS_FEMALE_1">
			<Text>Maia Stokeworth</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_THE_CROWNLANDS_FEMALE_2">
			<Text>Rosey</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_THE_CROWNLANDS_FEMALE_3">
			<Text>Annara Farring</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_THE_CROWNLANDS_FEMALE_4">
			<Text>Alyssa Velaryon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_THE_CROWNLANDS_FEMALE_5">
			<Text>Jeyne Waters</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Agendas-->

		<!--PEDIA-->
		<!--DISTRICTS-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_DRAGONPIT_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1">
			<Text>The Dragonpit is a huge, cavernous building that sits atop Rhaenys's hill in King's Landing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_DRAGONPIT_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2">
			<Text>The Targaryens would keep their dragons within the building. Thirty knights could ride abreast into its entrance. No pit dragon ever reached the size of the dragons who were raised before the construction of the building. When living dragons still nested beneath the dome light would shine through the windows at night.</Text>
		</Row>		
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_DRAGONPIT_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3">
			<Text>The Dragonpit's huge dome has collapsed within and its bronze or iron doors have been sealed for more than a century. It is a ruin, blackened by fire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_DRAGONPIT_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4">
			<Text>Prior to the Dragonpit, a great Sept was built on Rhaeny's Hill known as the Sept of Remembrance which used to be the main Sept in King's Landing. During the Faith Militant uprising, Maegor the Cruel, mounted on Balerion the Black Dread, incinerated the Great Sept with dragonflame and later decreed that a large domed structure would be built on the hill for Targaryens to house its royal dragons. Because Maegor had killed all those who had built the Red Keep to hide its secrets, many fled rather than work on the Dragonpit. Maegor had to use city prisoners, with supervisors from Myr and Volantis.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_DRAGONPIT_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5">
			<Text>King Aegon II's coronation took place in the Dragonpit. Later during the Targaryen civil war known as the Dance of the Dragons after King's Landing was captured by Queen Rhaenyra, the Dragonpit was destroyed during the Storming of the Dragonpit. When ten's of thousands of crazed and starving smallfolk led by the deranged Shepherd stormed the dragonpit to kill the dragons within. Five Targaryen dragons (Shrykos, Morghul, Tyraxes, Dreamfyre and Syrax) and thousands of smallfolk were killed. The dragonpit was reduced to flaming ruins.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_DRAGONPIT_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6">
			<Text>During the Great Spring Sickness so many people died so quickly that there was no time to bury the bodies. Instead they were piled up in the Dragonpit and when the corpses were 10 feet deep the Hand of the King, Lord Brynden Rivers, ordered the pyromancers to burn them. The light of the fires shone through the windows and by night citizens could see the dark green glow of wildfire all through King's Landing.</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!--CIV-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1">
			<Text>The crownlands is one of the nine constituent regions of the Seven Kingdoms of Westeros. It was never a sovereign nation, instead being contested by river kings, Storm Kings, and local petty kings until Aegon the Conqueror seized control of the area during his Wars of Conquest and made it his primary foothold on the continent. Since then, the crownlands have been ruled directly by the crown on the Iron Throne, first House Targaryen and, after Robert's Rebellion, House Baratheon. Bastards of noble origin raised in the crownlands are given the surname Waters.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2">
			<Text>The crownlands are based around Blackwater Bay, with the capital of King's Landing built where the Blackwater Rush meets the bay. King's Landing, the largest city in Westeros, contains the Great Sept of Baelor and the Red Keep, the home of House Baratheon of King's Landing. Settlements north of King's Landing include Antlers (seat of House Buckwell), Rosby (seat of House Rosby), Stokeworth (seat of House Stokeworth), and Duskendale (seat of House Rykker), the region's secondary port. Farther north are Rook's Rest (seat of House Staunton) and Crackclaw Point, a rugged peninsula of insular folk whose castles include the Dyre Den (seat of House Brune), Brownhollow (another seat of House Brune), and the Whispers (formerly of House Crabb). North of Crackclaw Point are the Bay of Crabs and the Vale of Arryn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3">
			<Text>The crownlands are bordered to the northwest and west by the riverlands. A stream forms part of the boundary between the two regions, with the hills of House Wode in the riverlands and the lands of House Hogg in the crownlands. An unnamed river flows south from Gods Eye into the Blackwater Rush in the western crownlands. Southwest of King's Landing are hills around Tumbleton in the Reach.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4">
			<Text>South of King's Landing is the kingswood, the royal hunting forest, and the stormlands. The Wendwater flows through the kingswood into the bay. East of the kingswood is Massey's Hook, another peninsula that with Crackclaw Point forms the inlet of Blackwater Bay. Castles on Massey's Hook include Stonedance (seat of House Massey) and Sharp Point (seat of House Bar Emmon).</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5">
			<Text>Islands within Blackwater Bay include Dragonstone (another seat of House Baratheon), Driftmark (seat of House Velaryon), and Claw Isle (seat of House Celtigar). Also sworn to the Baratheons of Dragonstone is Sweetport Sound (seat of House Sunglass). Massey's Hook is separated from Driftmark by the Gullet. East of Blackwater Bay is the narrow sea.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6">
			<Text>The kingsroad connects King's Landing with Storm's End to the south and the crossroads to the north, while the capital is connected to Lannisport by the goldroad and to Highgarden by the roseroad. With the exception of Crackclaw Point, the land is largely flat. Lying in the middle portion of Westeros, the crownlands possess a temperate climate.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7">
			<Text>The metropolis of King's Landing is the driving force of the region, with the largest population and harbor in the realm. Trade and taxes flow into the capital from every corner of the realm acknowledging the Iron Throne, and many foreign vessels ply their wares as well. Virtually every craft and trade is practiced here, from metalsmithing and shipbuilding to alchemy. Elsewhere, fishing and farming are the norm, with a smattering of the common professions.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_8">
			<Text>Along the kingsroad north of the capital, a traveler goes "past woods and orchards and neatly tended fields, through small villages, crowded market towns, and stout holdfasts."</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_9">
			<Text>In the Age of Heroes, the petty kings of House Darklyn ruled much of the future crownlands, from Duskendale to Crackclaw Point. Although neighboring realms forced them to swear fealty and their lands changed hands many times over the years, the Darklyns remained one of the more influential houses of the region. In the days of the Hundred Kingdoms, the mouth of the Blackwater was claimed by the Darklyns, the Masseys of Stonedance, and the river kings of Houses Mudd, Fisher, Bracken, Blackwood, and Hook. Two centuries before the Doom of Valyria, Valyrians settled Dragonstone and built a citadel as the westernmost outpost of the Valyrian Freehold, becoming another power in the region. In time, the middle of the narrow sea came to be controlled by the dragons of House Targaryen of Dragonstone, as well as the ships of House Velaryon of Driftmark and House Celtigar of Claw Isle.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_10">
			<Text>It was at the mouth of the Blackwater Rush, the later site of King's Landing, where Aegon Targaryen and his sisters, Visenya and Rhaenys, landed with their initial army. At that time the petty lords of the region had been subjugated by Harren the Black. Rosby and Stokeworth surrendered to Visenya and Rhaenys without fighting, while Aegon and his half-brother Orys Baratheon defeated the Darklyns and Mootons. Massey's Hook and the southern shore of the Blackwater Rush were controlled by the Storm Kings of House Durrandon, but the Bar Emmons and Masseys allied with Aegon the Conqueror against King Argilac the Arrogant.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_11">
			<Text>Since the Conquest, the crownlands houses have historically been a strong source of support for House Targaryen, with Crackclaw Point being particularly fierce supporters. The Conqueror's councillors included several crownlands men, including Crispian Celtigar, Daemon Velaryon, and Tristan Massey. Nobles from the region such as Qarlton Chelsted, a Hayford lord, and several Targaryens have served as Hand of the King, and even smallfolk of the region are near enough to catch the royal eye for such service, such as Rossart and presumably Septons Barth and Murmison. Nobles and smallfolk alike also provide much of the manpower for the City Watch of King's Landing. The Kingsguard has also included many men of the crownlands, such as Duncan the Tall, Donnel of Duskendale, the Cargyll twins, Ser Rickard Thorne, at least six men of Crackclaw Point, and seven Darklyn knights.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_12">
			<Text>At the start of the Dance of the Dragons, the Velaryons, supporters of Queen Rhaenyra Targaryen and the blacks, used their fleet to seal the Gullet and blockade King's Landing. King Aegon II Targaryen's supporters, the greens, retaliated by sacking Duskendale and Rook's Rest. The greens later broke the blockade with the Battle in the Gullet and sacked Driftmark. Rhaenyra was eventually fed to Aegon II's dragon, Sunfyre, at Dragonstone. At the end of the war, the Lads defeated Lord Borros Baratheon in the Battle of the Kingsroad.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_THE_CROWNLANDS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_13">
			<Text>The Defiance of Duskendale, a rising by the Darklyns during the reign of King Aerys II Targaryen, was a sign that even the normally loyal crownlands were losing respect for the dragonlords. Later, the outlaws of the Kingswood Brotherhood robbed nobles in the forest before being suppressed by the Kingsguard.</Text>
		</Row>		

		<!--LEADER-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_TITLE">
			<Text>Rhaegar Targaryen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_SUBTITLE">
			<Text>Prince of Dragonstone.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_QUOTE">
			<Text>He has a song. He is the prince that was promised, and his is the song of ice and fire. There must be one more. The dragon has three heads.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1">
			<Text>Prince Rhaegar Targaryen was the firstborn son of King Aerys II Targaryen and his sister-wife, Queen Rhaella. As heir-apparent, he was the Prince of Dragonstone and crown prince for the Iron Throne. Rhaegar was popular with the smallfolk during his lifetime, but he died in Robert's Rebellion which was triggered in part by his abduction of Lyanna Stark. He was slain in single combat by Robert Baratheon at the ruby ford during the battle of the Trident. Rhaegar was the elder brother of the exiled last members of House Targaryen, Prince Viserys and Princess Daenerys.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2">
			<Text>Rhaegar owned night-black plate armor, with the three-headed dragon of House Targaryen decorated in rubies on its breastplate, and underneath the plate he wore golden ringmail. Rhaegar decorated his helm with gold, orange, and red silken streamers resembling flames.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3">
			<Text>Rhaegar was an intelligent young man, who excelled at anything to which he put his mind, and grew to be a great knight and a skilled musician. The latter, however, held his preference; men said Rhaegar loved his silver-stringed harp more than he loved his lance. Jorah Mormont has described Rhaegar as valiant, honorable, and noble while Barristan Selmy has called him determined, deliberate, dutiful, and single-minded. The crown prince was said to have been uninterested in the play of other children as a boy, but bookish "to a fault". He learned to read at such an early age that people jested that his mother Rhaella had swallowed some books and a candle during her pregnancy. Later in life, however, Rhaegar did acquire several trusted and loyal companions. Rhaegar was deeply affected by "the shadow of Summerhall", because he was "born in grief" and was considered melancholic at times. At the same time, Summerhall was also Rhaegar's favorite place.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4">
			<Text>The prince was well-loved by the people of the Seven Kingdoms during his lifetime and is still fondly remembered to this day. While Robert Baratheon despises Rhaegar and accuses him of having raped Lyanna Stark, the only thought of Eddard Stark, Lyanna's brother, is he did not think Rhaegar frequented brothels. Jaime Lannister remembers the iron tones of Rhaegar's voice. Barristan Selmy, who served three kings, thinks that Rhaegar would have been better than any of them. His sister, Daenerys, is frequently compared to Rhaegar as a compliment. People who had romantic feelings toward Rhaegar include Cersei Lannister and Jon Connington.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5">
			<Text>Prince Rhaegar was the firstborn son of King Aerys II Targaryen and Queen Rhaella. He was born at Summerhall in 259 AC, on the same day as the great tragedy there. As a child he read obsessively, to the point that jests were made about his habits. He became a noted warrior later in life, although he did not initially seem inclined to martial habits. However, apparently by something he had read, Rhaegar became motivated to become a warrior.[NEWLINE]At the age of seventeen, Rhaegar was knighted, and from all reports grew into a highly skilled and capable fighter, always distinguishing himself well at tournaments, although he seldom entered the lists - he never loved the song of swords the way that men like Robert Baratheon or Jaime Lannister did.[NEWLINE]Rhaegar's squires were Myles Mooton and Richard Lonmouth, and after he knighted them they remained close companions. Jon Connington, whom he had squired with, was a good friend to Rhaegar as well. Returning from a trip to Dorne, Rhaegar once visited the Connington seat of Griffin's Roost. His songs brought the castle's women to tears, while Lord Armond Connington sought House Targaryen's support against rival House Morrigen. Rhaegar's closest and oldest friend, however, was Ser Arthur Dayne, the Sword of the Morning, trusting him more than Ser Barristan Selmy.[NEWLINE]Rhaegar often liked to visit the ruins of Summerhall with only his harp and when he returned he sang songs of such beauty they could reduce women to tears. Although Rhaegar was often dour, private and bookish, Cersei Lannister noted at the tournament in honor of Viserys's birth in Lannisport in 276 AC that the smallfolk cheered for Lord Tywin Lannister twice as much as for King Aerys II, but only half as loudly for Tywin as for Rhaegar. Rhaegar fought well in the tourney besting a dozen skilled knights, among them Barristan Selmy, Gerion, and Tygett Lannister but was defeated in the champion's tilt by his friend Arthur Dayne. Aerys refused Tywin's offer at the tourney to betroth Cersei to Rhaegar. Rhaegar defeated Arthur in the tourney at Storm's End.[NEWLINE]Rhaegar was born at a time when the Targaryen's had declined, and once he came of age, there was no sister, or anyone else of their bloodline, available for him to marry. King Aerys sent his first cousin, Lord Steffon Baratheon, to seek a bride for Rhaegar. Despite Valyrian blood still being present in Essos, Steffon could not find appropriate females of noble-enough birth for Rhaegar to wed.[NEWLINE]After this in early 279 AC, Rhaegar was formally betrothed to the Dornish princess, Elia Martell, the younger sister of Doran Martell, Prince of Dorne. They married the following year in 280 AC, a lavish ceremony was held at the Great Sept of Baelor. His father did not attend the wedding as he was paranoid about an assassination attempt and nor did he permit the young Prince Viserys to attend. Rhaegar and his father's relationship was straining at this point, and he and his new bride took up residence on Dragonstone instead of King's Landing. Rhaegar and Elia had their first child, a girl named Rhaenys, in 280 AC. When the babe was presented at court, Rhaegar's mother, Queen Rhaella, embraced her grandchild warmly while King Aerys remarked: "she smells Dornish". The relationship between Aerys and Rhaegar became more and more estranged.[NEWLINE]Elia and Rhaegar had a son they named Aegon. Elia, due to her delicate health, was bed-ridden for half a year after giving birth to Rhaenys and nearly died giving birth to Aegon, after which the maesters told Rhaegar she would be unable to have any more children.[NEWLINE]Maester Aemon, whom Rhaegar corresponded with via raven messages, remembers that Rhaegar believed his child Aegon to be the prince that was promised.[NEWLINE]When Lord Tywin resigned his position as Hand of the King and left court, the new focus of King Aerys's mistrust and paranoia was his own son and heir, Prince Rhaegar. At court, there was growing tension between factions loyal to the king and to the prince. Grand Maester Pycelle dispatched a letter to the Citadel, writing that tensions and division at court strongly resembled those before the Dance of the Dragons. Pycelle was fearful a civil war would break out unless some accord could be reached that would satisfy both factions.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6">
			<Text>In either 280 AC or 281 AC, Lord Walter Whent announced a tourney would be held at Harrenhal to rival any previous tournament. It is believed by some that the tourney was secretly arranged and financed by Prince Rhaegar, as a pretext, so Rhaegar could meet up with the great lords of the realm to discuss arranging a Great Council and the removal of his father. The tournament was announced by Walter shortly after his brother, Ser Oswell of the Kingsguard, visited his older brother. When Lord Varys alerted Aerys II to this possibility, the king decided to attend the tourney. During the great tourney at Harrenhal, Rhaegar seemed unstoppable and defeated even Ser Arthur Dayne. Taking the winter rose crown for the queen of love and beauty, he revealed his interest in Lyanna Stark by passing over his wife, Princess Elia of Dorne, and setting it in Lyanna's lap. Eddard Stark later recalled that moment as "when all the smiles died". The next year, Rhaegar seemingly kidnapped Lyanna, for reasons unknown. This act ultimately triggered Robert's Rebellion and the downfall of the Targaryen dynasty.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!--UNITS-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_TARGARYEN_DRAGON_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1">
			<Text>Dragons are magical creatures, which existed on the continents of Westeros and Essos, but are considered to have been extinct for almost one hundred and fifty years. The only remaining traces of the dragons are skeletal remains and dragon eggs which are thought to have turned to stone.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_TARGARYEN_DRAGON_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2">
			<Text>Dragons are scaled, reptilian creatures. They have four limbs: two wings, which are used as forelegs like bats and pterosaurs, and two rear legs.  Dragons have strong jaws, sharp teeth and claws, leathery wings and long necks and tails, with horns upon their heads. As young hatchlings, they are around the size of a cat. Provided it has food and freedom, a dragon never stops growing. A dragon given such freedom can reach a span width of twenty feet within a year and a half. Dragons which are locked up, e.g., the Targaryen dragons housed in the Dragonpit in King's Landing, do not grow as large as dragons left free to fly as they wish. Although increasing age means increasing size, a larger size is not always an indication of a higher age (e.g., the younger Meraxes was larger than the older Vhagar). Balerion, the largest Targaryen dragon, was large enough to swallow an aurochs or a mammoth from Ibben whole. The polished skulls of the Targaryen dragons look like glittering onyx, and their teeth like curved daggers of black diamond. Dragonbones are black due to their high iron content.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_TARGARYEN_DRAGON_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3">
			<Text>It is said that dragons are fire made flesh. Great heat emanates from dragons' bodies, to the point that they steam during cold nights. Dragons only eat cooked meat, and use the extremely hot flame which they breathe to cook their meat before eating it. Dragonbone is as strong as steel, but lighter and far more flexible. The dragon's bones are utterly impervious to fire. A dragon's scales are largely, but not entirely, impervious to flame as well, and serve as protection for the more vulnerable flesh and musculature beneath. As a dragon ages, its scales thicken and grow harder, affording even more protection, leaving dragons nearly immune to fire, although they can still be wounded by dragonflame (e.g., Moondancer's eyes being blinded by Sunfyre's fire during the Dance of the Dragons). Similarly, as dragons age, the fires they breath become hotter and fiercer. Where a hatchling's flame can set straw aflame, the flames of older dragons, like Balerion and Vhagar in the fullness of their power, could melt steel and stone. The lifespan of dragons is many times that of a human. Balerion, the largest and oldest Targaryen dragon, already alive when House Targaryen relocated from Valyria to Dragonstone in 128 BC died of old age in 94 AC[17] during the reign of King Jaehaerys I Targaryen, near two hundred years of age. Dragons are believed to be intrinsically tied to magic in the world. Since the death of the last dragon in 153 AC, summers grew shorter and the winters colder and crueler, while magical spells became less powerful.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_TARGARYEN_DRAGON_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4">
			<Text>Historians, like Septon Barth, Grand Maester Munkun, and Maester Thomax, hold markedly divergent views on the mating habits of dragons. Dragons lay large, scaled eggs to reproduce. According to Archmaester Gyldayn, and agreed upon by Maester Yandel, the ability of a dragon to lay eggs is proof that said dragon is female. When a dragon is never observed to have laid eggs, this is taking as proof that it must have been male. However, according to Septon Barth and Maester Aemon, dragons have no fixed gender, but are “now one and now the other, as changeable as flame”, Septon Barth believes that dragons can change sex at need, but Maester Anson believes this to be erroneous, and states in his Truth that Barth's statement is simply a misunderstood esoteric metaphor. Dragons believed to be female, e.g., Syrax, Dreamfyre, Tessarion, and Meleys, are referred to as a she-dragon. The dragon Caraxes has thusfar been referred to as both male and female. Traditionally, Targaryen princes received a dragon's egg in their cradle, allowing them to bond with the dragons as soon as the eggs hatched. Un-hatched eggs can become fossilized at an old age.</Text>
		</Row>		

		<!--CIVINFO-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_THE_CROWNLANDS_LOCATION">
			<Text>The Crownlands</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_THE_CROWNLANDS_SIZE">
			<Text>The crownlands are based around Blackwater Bay, with the capital of King's Landing built where the Blackwater Rush meets the bay. King's Landing, the largest city in Westeros, contains the Great Sept of Baelor and the Red Keep, the home of House Baratheon of King's Landing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_THE_CROWNLANDS_POPULATION">
			<Text>The metropolis of King's Landing is the driving force of the region, with the largest population and harbor in the realm.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_THE_CROWNLANDS_CAPITAL">
			<Text>King's Landing</Text>
		</Row>

		<!--DIPLO-->

		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>I appreciate your loyalty.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>I hear things about your comments on my father. I don't like it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>I propse instead of swords, how about sit down together and battle with harps?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>I should sing for today.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>Let me work on another composing and come back...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>I will require a sword and armor. It seems I must be a warrior.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>When the battle's done I mean to call a council. Changes will be made. I meant to do it long ago, but ... well, it does no good to speak of roads not taken. We shall talk when I return.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>Tributes well received.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>I don't think it's a good idea to have your men put some crazy ideas into my father's head.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>I've semt a royal envoy to you. And he will play my new song in your dinning hall for me.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>And I will call this treason.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>Ruling isn't only about power. Your people should like you. Your people should create great works for you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_REASON_FROM_AI_LEADER_ANY_REASON_AGENDA_HARP_OVER_SWORD_LOW_CULTURE">
			<Text>(You have low culture.)</Text>
		</Row>		
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>Greetings stranger. You are speaking to Ser Rhaegar Targaryen, Prince of Dragonstone. Common folks also call me Silver prince. I am more a singer than warrior. Maybe I am better than any of the bards in your realm.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>I will show you the way to Red Keep. Please ignore my father. He's always threatening people with "burn them all" mumbles recently.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>How is your realm looking? I should probably sing a song for it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>Tell me about your throne. Is it spiky? Mine hurts me when I sat on it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>Sȳz naejot ūndegon ao.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_EXIT_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>I'm impressed on your unique culture. We should exchange our understandings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_DESCRIPTION_HIGH_CULTURE">
			<Text>Rhaegar is pleased to see you with high culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_EXIT_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>If your people don't sing for you, you must be a terrible leader.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_DESCRIPTION_LOW_CULTURE">
			<Text>Rhaegar is upset by your low culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>A ture dragon has three heads. We need alliances for being strong.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>Knee, and you will find me very forgiving.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>This time, I really agree with my father on burning you all.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>I'd rather being a singer than a warrior. I propose an end to our conflict and get back on table for the matters.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>You may pass. But don't get too close to the Dragonpit. Dragons aren't very friendly to strangers.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>Our dragons see your people as food. For you own safety, no.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>On behalf of the King, I demand you open your border for us. Land and air.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>Your army out there is considered an act of treason. Do you want to make it official?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>He has a song. He is the prince that was promised, and his is the song of ice and fire. I've lost him, I...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>We are not agreed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_RHAEGAR_TARGARYEN_ANY">
			<Text>Generous offer. We accpet.</Text>
		</Row>
		
	</BaseGameText>
</GameData>
